Just as I thought, Joseph's
Blood suits me well.
It's like it was meant to be
mine from the very beginning.
It's far more intense than
anything I've ever felt before.
This sensation is absolutely incredible!
A century ago, this body
belonged to Jonathan Joestar.
And now these hands have feasted on
the blood of his grandson, Joseph.
But it was you, Jotaro, who
so thoughtfully led me here.
Your ancestor must be ruling in his grave.
You Joestars have always been a nuisance,
so I think the time has
come to put you self
-righteous cretins in your
proper place beneath my boot.
But, in the end, Jotaro,
it would appear that the Joestar's destiny
is to facilitate my
ascension to perfection!
Who are you? Dio?
Old man...
You have to stay calm.
From here on, no matter what
Dio does to me, keep your cool.
Focus.
Tempting as it may be, never allow
yourself to succumb to anger.
Don't worry about my fate, Jotaro.
I've accepted that it was meant to be.
Wait a sec.
That's his soul?
But how?
Kakyoin deciphered the mystery of Dio's
stand, and I imparted that knowledge to you.
Had we attacked Dio together
before learning his secret,
he would have been able
to easily kill all of us.
You now have the ability to
move while time is frozen,
but you only have two or three seconds.
Make sure you use that time wisely.
Remember what I told you, Jotaro.
You mustn't lose your head.
If you lose control, it'll only backfire.
Keep your emotions in check
when you face off with Dio.
Jotaro.
It's been quite the journey, eh, my boy?
An unforgettable adventure.
Call me crazy.
But our time together was a lot of fun
more fun than I've had in a long time
That was real right hey,
what are you looking at?
You bastard!
He's been sucked dry.
I know you said to keep my
emotions in check, but screw that.
He just crossed the line.
There's not a person on the planet
who can stay calm after seeing that.
This fight has come to an end.
No, I will, nor did I die.
I'll be абсолют.
I've got a word on my
mind to find a boundary.
If it was the end, I'll get lost.
I'll be in the middle of the story.
I'll Guild of the Church.
I live with a dream,
So now, what we are doing is now.
I'm going to keep going.
I'm going to be a good one.
On the last page of the last page?
Wonderful.
O la la la...
O la la...
The world!
Bring time to a halt!
One second, two seconds,
and three seconds!
Now four!
Five seconds. Interesting.
Six seconds.
My, my.
This makes seven seconds.
My power grows exponentially.
I can stop time for even longer!
But as for you, Jotaro, you wasted
the opportunity you had to move.
Gambling on getting me two seconds
before time resumed was all for naught.
What a miscalculation!
I feel so marvelous.
I could serenade the world.
The moment I've dreamed of for
so long is finally upon us.
Eight seconds have passed.
I've been an immortal being
for an entire century.
But never in my wildest
dreams could I have
imagined I'd feel something
this exhilarating.
The blood of the Joe Stars
courses through my veins.
Guess you were right after all, old man.
My stupid temper got me
in a shit ton of trouble.
For Christ's sake.
No, this isn't the end.
He still hasn't faced the
full force of my rage.
Nine seconds total.
That's how long my power
lasted just now. Yes.
Perhaps nine seconds is the new extent
of my stand's extraordinary power.
You bastard.
Now to unleash all of my Stan's power!
Jotaro, weren't you mumbling
something about being angry?
Is this all the power you possess?
And now I shall administer
the killing blow!
Here it is, my final dance with time!
Nine more seconds,
that's all you have left!
Prepare to die, the world!
One second.
Two seconds.
Three seconds.
Jotaro couldn't figure out why Dio had
suddenly vanished amidst the standstill.
Four seconds.
But he pushed the
thoughts out of his mind.
No matter what sinister
plot Dio was hatching?
No matter what unholy tack
he attempted to unleash?
Jotaro had only two seconds to respond.
Only two seconds to drive Star Platinum's
fists into Dio once and for all.
Five seconds.
I've had just about enough
of this neon vampire.
The next time I see that
goddamn face of his,
I'm going to freaking lose it
and beat him into the ground.
Six seconds.
That's right, Dio.
Come and get it.
Seven seconds.
I'm going to roll all over you!
No!
It's too late!
Time to die!
Eight seconds!
I'll obliterate you!
Nine seconds.
I did it.
It's over.
The world has defeated Star Platinum.
My stand is more powerful than his.
I am immortal.
I am everlasting.
Stand power!
Now there is incontrovertible
proof that no one
on this miserable planet
is stronger than me.
You loathsome humans.
I shall rule over your pathetic
species until the end of time.
Now bow before my wisdom and power.
Ten seconds.
Would you look at that?
I can stop time for ten seconds.
All right.
Now that I've defeated Jotaro,
I should inspect his lifeless
body and drink his blood.
That is, if there's any
blood left to save her.
This can't be.
My body's slowing down.
What's happening?
No, it's not that I'm slowing down.
For some reason, I can't move at all.
I don't get it.
This is impossible. I'm frozen.
Hey, Dio.
It's been 11 seconds.
I guess that's your stand's limit, huh?
What?
I stopped time at 9 seconds,
and it's a good thing I did.
It gave me a chance to escape.
Good grief, you idiot.
Here's the thing.
Since you're frozen like that,
destroying you will only take a second.
This is madness.
You can stop time, too? Curse you.
This whole act was a ruse to waste my
nine seconds, wasn't it, you bastard?
How does it feel, Dio? Tell me.
How's it feel having your arch enemy tower
behind you while you
stand frozen and helpless?
I suppose it's a lot like holding
your breath while underwater
only someone's out to get you
and your air is running out as
you desperately swim for your
life then after finally reaching
the surface and taking a breath
you get pulled right back in?
Sound familiar?
But after everything you've done to you
you're not gonna get any sympathy from me.
Time is about to start moving again.
Compassion is something you're
never gonna get from me.
I haven't got any kindness for
your sorry United ass though.
I gotta admit you look pretty pathetic
writhing on the ground in agony.
As much as i want to killing you like this
would leave a pretty
bad taste in my mouth.
I wonder how long it'll
take for you to heal?
Three seconds? Four?
Maybe the very moment your legs are healed
star platinum's headed
your way to demolish you.
If this were the wild west
the hero would say it's
high noon now get off the
ground and draw your peace.
Dio you're getting one shot
This insignificant whelp.
How dare he mock me?
Oh, I shouldn't be surprised.
Of course you would use this opportunity
to make such a human declaration.
You think like a true mortal, cursed with
a fleeting life destined for obscurity.
A bad taste in your mouth, you say?
What, are you afraid
you'd regret killing me?
That reasoning is as
pathetic as your species.
Your foolish honor will be your demise.
That is where you and I differ.
My vision is clear and my mind
is focused on a single goal.
I want to dominate.
Nothing more, nothing less.
It's the only thing that
will bring me fulfillment.
But how I go about doing that
doesn't matter in the slightest.
There!
How about a little blood in your eyes?
I win! Die!
What the hell?
It's impossible!
I am the immortal Dia!
I am Dia!
When the sun comes up,
you'll be nothing but dust.
You only made one mistake.
One that got you killed.
Dio, this whole thing might
have ended differently, but...
You and him pissed me off.
Was it worth it?
This is Speedwagon Foundation, car two.
We're traveling northbound
on the Al Neal Expressway,
and we've retrieved Dio's remains.
I repeat, we've retrieved Dio's remains.
Dio's body is showing cellular activity.
He must be exposed to
sunlight immediately.
Proceed with extreme caution. Roger.
Noriyaki Kakyoin is dead.
His body is being transported now.
Jean-Pierre Polnareff is unconscious.
The medical staff of car one has him.
Roger.
Car two, I have a question.
Why have you placed the remains of Dio
and Joseph Joestar in the same car?
Because it's not over yet.
Dio borrowed something from us. Huh?
And we need to take it
back from the bastard.
I'm not following your train of thought.
I need you to perform a blood
transfusion between the two bodies.
Huh?
That's absurd.
You want us to transfuse
Dio's blood into Mr.
Joestar? I see.
You're trying to bring him back to life.
It hasn't been all that long
since Dio drained his blood.
His upper half was destroyed in the
fight, but we'll take as much as we can.
If we hurry, I think we can make it.
hey car one did you
catch all that over roger
it's impossible he doesn't
even have a pulse right
not to mention his heart
is stopped which means
we couldn't circulate
his blood if we wanted to
don't give me that you
could call everything
we've done on this journey
impossible i'm tired of
hearing words like
impossible or futile they all
mean nothing to us you
can do it if his heart's
beating, right?
Well, you're in luck.
Thanks to Dio, I've already had a bit of
practice with stopping and starting hearts.
I hear a pulse! Yes, you're right!
His heart is beating!
We have to transfuse his blood into Mr.
Joestar quickly!
We might just be able to pull this off!
Remarkable!
Take a look at his skin.
It's completely regaining all its color.
His skin is filling out.
My god, brain activity too.
I don't believe it.
His vitals are stable as well.
His eyes!
He opened his eyes!
We did it! He's back!
Old man.
You're a damn fool, Jotaro!
You have got to be kidding!
Hmm.
All you've done is resurrect yours truly!
Bastard! Wait! Calm down,
Jojaro! It was a joke!
I was just kidding!
There's no need to get violent!
I'm sorry!
I was just trying to have some fun!
You have my word! It's me!
I'm Joseph Joestar!
I was born September 27th in 1920!
My wife's name is Suzy Q, and
I collect comics as a hobby!
I have a question for you.
Who's the leading actress
in Tarzan the Ape Man?
Bo Derek!
Okay, now answer this one.
Who sang Eat It, the spoof of Beat It?
Weird Al Yankovic!
Good grief.
It has to be you.
Who else would know
pointless crap like that?
This is Card, over!
It's amazing! Mr.
Joestar is back with us!
He's come back from the brink of death!
It's a miracle! Over!
Hear that?
We've taken back everything
you stole from us.
Do you?
It's finally over.
Dio took something
precious from all of us.
For a hundred years, he's
taken whatever he wanted.
His appetite for power
has been insatiable.
He's taken far too much.
You realize that?
Yeah, he's taken things from us that
we'll never be able to get back.
The losses that we've endured on this
journey stretch as far as the planet itself.
But thanks to their sacrifices,
we're here to tell the tale
and carry on in their stead.
Kakyoin. Iggy. Avdol.
It's over.
So you're really going
back to France, Polnareff?
This may be a bit forward,
but your family's gone.
Why don't you come back
with me to New York?
Mr.
Joestar, I know they're gone, but
France is the only home I've ever known.
It's filled with memories.
It's a place I must return
to no matter where I go.
But if you ever need anything,
all you have to do is call and
I'll be there in a heartbeat.
We're gonna miss you, buddy.
It wasn't easy, that's for damn sure.
But I had a hell of a time,
and I'm lucky to have been on
this adventure with you guys.
Remember, we're a team, and
that's never gonna change.
Calling all passengers for
France International Airlines.
Flight 92 to Paris.
Please proceed to gate 18.
Avianto, you ornery bastard.
Live long and happy.
And you as moody grandson,
you'd better not forget me.
We'll meet again.
That is, of course, if you
don't hate my guts by then.
Stubborn jackass.
We wouldn't be able to forget about
you, even if we wanted to, Polnareff.
You be well.
Au River.
Yeah.
See you later.
Holly!
How are you sitting up
straight all of a sudden?
I'm feeling much better.
I'm not sure how to put it into words.
It's as if we could
read each other's minds.
What?
Mom, I can feel that
they're coming home to us.
Oh, Polly!
Papa and my Jotaro!
They're coming home!
Thank you.